[{"answer": "Clearly, this could have been worse, but it was pretty bad out there.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "Vermont reeling from the worst flooding since the '20s, but was Irene overblown?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "Better to be safe than sorry.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Did government and the media go too far?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, there is a lot of resentment here in Vermont when people say this was hyped.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Did people know what may be coming?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "UCHMAN: We don't think it will go much higher, but we do think it will go higher.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "What was the general feeling about the scenes that we are witnessing and the possible casualty toll?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Obviously our heart goes out to the victims who are in the affected areas both on the west side of the state in those tributaries like the Winooski that feed into Lake Champlain and on the east of the state in the Connecticut River Basin.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "When you see what's happening in Vermont, what do you feel about it?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a partial truth that is fundamentally inaccurate though at its base.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "What do you say to those who say that the media, including CNN and others, hyped up this hurricane and that it wasn't as bad as everyone said it was going to be?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "The problem with Irene is that for wind it was an underachiever.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "But in terms of how the power and the strength and therefore the threat of Hurricane Irene changing in that very crucial last 24 hours, could that have been predicted at all or can the authorities only really ever go on what's right in front of them at any given moment?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Well, from an official point of view, we really had to make decisions based on what we were hearing from the National Weather Service and other hurricane and governmental experts.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "What is your view from an official point of view?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "You know, the snow response was absolutely an unacceptable response.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "How would you respond to that?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Yes, I was down in Nags Head feeling the winds a couple of days ago and I was still finding sand in my hair and my ears this morning.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "No, Piers, that's not what I'm saying.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "How many have to be killed before you assess this as serious enough to take the measures they took?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "I have looked at all the other storms that were the same pressure.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "What do you have to say?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Faced with the exactly same set of circumstances, would you do exactly the same thing again?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Well, remember, social media is a great tool.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Is it a different thing when you're dealing with a hurricane with mass flooding and so on?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Look, I'm a person of faith.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "You're going to raise hell, have you?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "That's true.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Yeah, 40.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "You know, I like my jet.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "What would you prefer?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "It's the American way.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "That's the American way, right?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "America loves second chances.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Is it ethically right that he should be able to do this, given what he was found guilty of?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "If you could have signed him, would you have done?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "You know, I try to get to know our guys.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Would you have had any moral problem with it?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I'm not allowed to talk about my current team.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Any knuckleheads on your current team?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "What do you think of that, as a former contender yourself.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "is she really?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "I learned that -- you know, I started with nothing.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "What's the business ethos of Mark Cuban?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Mark@hd.net.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Can they e- mail you if they watch this?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "I read them first.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "How quickly do you respond?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "The minute they start with a sob story.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "When do you immediately delete?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Oh, my goodness.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "What's been your biggest failure?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Going to take a little break.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "If you are not willing to put in the effort, if you're not willing to commit everything, why would I invest in you?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Done.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Are you prepared to do that?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "No quite, but he's intense.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Is he like Ari Gold?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "UBAN: No, it's not right.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "He's failed, but not through faults of his own.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Do you think he's given America that or has he failed America?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "They all could make a president.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Who of the Republican candidates do you think could make potentially a president?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "None of them yet, because -- all for the same reason.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Who would make a good one?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "You have done everything else.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Are you kidding me?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "It was amazing.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Looking back at it, how did it feel to you?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "There's actually -- I watched the video, and I just screamed.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "The moment you knew you had won, what was going through your head?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "I thought of my dad.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Did you think of anybody?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "I'm not going to buy another sports team.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "If enough Americans decided they quite like Mark Cuban to work his magic on America that he's worked for the Mavericks, what would you say?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "I am absolutely serious.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "Only God knows.", "docId": "110829pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Can we expert the little patter of little Beyonce and Jay-Zs?", "qSentId": 705}]